shocking.link 2015-06-01

# Privacy Policy - Shocking Links

**Privacy Policy**

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

**(1) Credit Card Details**

During checkout you will be asked to enter your payment details on the payment page.

This page is encrypted with SSL security.

We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties.

**(2) Cookies**

A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

We may use both “session” cookies and “persistent” cookies on the website. We will use the session cookies to: keep track of you whilst you navigate the website. We will use the persistent cookies to: enable our website to recognise you when you visit.

We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google’s privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. (For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector.) This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites including this one.

**(3) Using your personal data**

Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

We may use your personal information to:

administer the website;  
improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;  
enable your use of the services available on the website;  
send to you goods purchased via the website, and supply to you services purchased via the website;  
send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;  
send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;  
send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;  
send to you marketing communications relating to our business which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications);  
deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website;  
Where you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the license you grant to us.

**(4) Disclosures**

We may disclose information about you to any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.  
In addition, we may disclose information about you:

to the extent that we are required to do so by law;  
in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;  
in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and  
to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling.  
Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

**(5) International data transfers**

Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

If you are in the European Economic Area (EEA), information which you provide may be transferred to countries which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the EEA.

You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information.

**(6) Security of your personal data**

We will take all reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

**(7) Policy amendments**

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

**(8) Your rights**

You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information may be subject to the payment of a fee (currently fixed at £10.00).

You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email at any time. (In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal data for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal data for marketing purposes.)

**(9) Third party websites**

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.

**(10) Updating information**

Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.

**(11) Contact**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by at: info@shocking.link
